thefinancebuff.com 2013-04-12

# Privacy Policy - The Finance Buff

The privacy of visitors to The Finance Buff is important to us.

At The Finance Buff, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use or visit The Finance Buff, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## E-Mail Addresses

The WordPress blog software we use requires an e-mail address when you add a comment to a blog post. It does not have to be a real e-mail address unless you want to use the “notify me of followup comments via e-mail” feature. Please use [anon@example.com](mailto:anon@example.com) if you don’t want to enter your real e-mail address. Whether you enter your real e-mail address or not, it will not be published. We do not use your e-mail address for marketing or disclose your e-mail address to any third party unless required by law.

When you subscribe to blog updates by e-mail using the service provided by Feedburner, or when you contact us using the contact form, we can see your e-mail address. Like the e-mail address entered in blog comments, we do not use your e-mail address for marketing or disclose your e-mail address to any third party unless required by law.

## Web Analytics Data

As with most other web sites, we collect and use data from third-party web analytics services. The information provided by the web analytics services include your IP address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider, such as Verizon or Cox Cable), the browser you used to visit the site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited the site and which pages you visited throughout the site. These are not personally identifiable information.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

The site uses cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit the site. This could include remembering the information you entered last time when you add a new comment.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies from this site or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
